摩根
Morgan.
我不知道你还在不在
I don't know if you're out there.
我不知道你能不能听到
I don't know if you can hear me.
也许你现在在听
Maybe you're listening right now.
希望如此
I hope so.
我找到了其他人　我的家人
I found others… my family,
难以置信吧
If you can believe it.
我的妻子和儿子
My wife and son,
他们还活着
They're alive.
我想告诉你这点
I wanted you to know that.
还有一点你要知道
There's something else you need to know.
亚特兰大不是我们想的那样
Atlanta isn't what we thought.
不是他们保证的那样　那座城市…
It's not what they promised. The city is…
不要进入城市
Do not enter the city.
里面已是行尸的天下
It belongs to the dead now.
我们在西北部几英里外有营地
We're camped a few miles northwest,
就在一座被遗弃的大型采石场边上
Up by a big abandoned rock quarry.
你可以在地图上看到
You can see it on a map.
希望你能找到我们
I hope you come find us.
但你务必要小心
But be careful.
昨晚有行尸从树林里出来袭击我们
Last night walkers came out of the woods.
我们伤亡惨重
We lost people.
你自己小心　摩根　照顾好你儿子
Watch yourself, Morgan. Take care of your boy.
明天凌晨我会再和你联系
I'll try you again tomorrow at dawn.
安德莉亚
Andrea.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
她已经去了
She's gone.
你得让我们处理
You got to let us take her.
我们都很关心她
We all cared about her.
我保证我们会尽量下手轻点
And I promise we'll be as gentle as we can.
她还是一动不动吗
She still won't move?
她甚至连话都不说
She won't even talk to us.
她都这样一晚上了
She's been there all night.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
不能让艾米的尸体这么留着
Can't just leave Amy like that.
我们得像对其他人一样
We need to deal with it.
把她处理掉
same as the others.
我来和她说
I'll tell her how it is.
安德莉亚
Andrea.
这次我可开了保险了
I know how the safety works.
好吧　行了
All right. Okay.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
《行尸走肉》
你们大脑进水了吧
Y'all can't be serious.
让一个妞儿妨碍我们
Let that girl hamstring us?
那死了的女孩就是个定时炸弹
The dead girl's a time bomb.
你有什么好主意
What do you suggest?
一箭射过去
Take the shot.
干净利落　直接命中脑子
Clean, in the brain from here.
老子从这距离都能射中火鸡脑门中央
Hell, I can hit a turkey between the eyes from this distance.
不行　上帝啊　让她一个人呆会
No. For god's sakes, let her be.
别发愣了　小吉　我们还有活要干
Wake up, Jimbo. We've got some work to do.
多谢
Thanks.
你们在搞什么
What are you guys doing?
这是堆僵尸的　我们的人堆在那儿
This is for geeks. Our people go over there.
有什么区别　他们都被感染了
What's the difference? They're all infected.
我们的人得堆在那里
Our people go in that row over there.
我们不能烧了他们
We don't burn them!
我们得埋葬他们
We bury them.
明白了吗
Understand?
把我们的人堆去那边
Our people go in that row over there.
你们都活该
You reap what you sow.
你少说句会死啊　哥们
You know what? Shut up, man.
你们把我哥哥丢下等死
Y'all left my brother for dead.
这是你们咎由自取
You had this coming.
你在流血吗
Are you bleeding?
从尸体上沾到的
I just got some on me from the bodies.
那是鲜血　你被咬了吗
That blood is fresh. Were you bit?
没有
No.
我在袭击中被擦到了
I got scratched during the attack.
- 你被咬了　-我没事
- You got bit. - I'm fine.
那让我看看
Then show me.
- 别告诉别人　求你了　-他被行尸咬了
- Don't tell, please. - A walker got him.
他被行尸咬了
A walker bit jim.
- 我没事　-让我们看看
- I'm okay. I'm okay. - Show it to us.
快让我们看看
Show it to us.
- 别紧张　吉姆　-抓住他
- Easy, Jim. - Grab him.
吉姆　放下那玩意
Jim, put it down. Put it down.
我没事　我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
我说直接给他脑门上来一下
I say we put a pickaxe in his head.
把那个死掉的女孩一起处理掉
And the dead girl's and be done with it.
如果是你的话　你也想这样吗
Is that what you'd want if it were you?
没错　我还要为此感谢你们
Yeah, and I'd thank you while you did it.
我也没想到我会这么说
I hate to say it… I never thought I would…
但也许达里尔说得对
But maybe Daryl's right.
吉姆不是怪物或咬人的疯狗　戴尔
Jim's not a monster, Dale, or some rabid dog.
- 我不是说…　-他病了　他是个病人
- I'm not suggesting… - He's sick. A sick man.
这事一开始就刹不了车了　我们的界限在哪里
We start down that road, where do we draw the line?
界限很清楚　绝不能允许僵尸的存在
The line's pretty clear. Zero tolerance for walkers,
- 准僵尸也不行　-如果我们能帮他呢
- Or them to be. - What if we can get him help?
我听说疾控中心在研制解药
I heard the C.D.C. Was working on a cure.
我也听说了很多事
I heard that too. Heard a.
但世界末日了什么都拉倒了
lot of things before the world went to hell.
如果疾控中心还在运行呢
What if the c.D.C. Is still up and running?
- 哥们　这可有点勉强了　-为什么
- Man, that is a stretch right there. - Why?
如果还有政府机构　不管剩下什么
If there's any government left, any structure at all,
他们一定不惜一切代价保护疾控中心　是吧
They'd protect the C.D.C. At all costs, wouldn't they?
这是我们最好的机会　稳定居所　安全保障
I think it's our best shot. Shelter, protection…
得　瑞克　你想要那些　好　我也想要啊
Okay, Rick, you want those things, all right? I do too, okay?
如果它们真的存在　肯定也是在军事基地里
Now if they exist, they're at the army base.
- 本宁堡　-那可是另一头的100英里外
- Fort Benning. - That's 100 miles in the opposite direction.
对　但那里远离危险区域
That is right. But it's away from the hot zone.
听我说　如果那些地方仍在运作
Now listen to me. If that place is operational,
肯定是戒备森严　我们会很安全
It'll be heavily armed. We'd be safe there.
军队肯定站在对抗僵尸的第一线
The military were on the front lines of this thing.
他们被全灭了　我们都见到了
They got overrun. We've all seen that.
疾控中心是我们最好的选择　也是吉姆的唯一希望
The C.D.C. is our best choice and Jim's only chance.
你去找阿司匹林去吧　爱咋咋地
You go looking for aspirin, do what you need to do.
果然还是得靠有种的人来
Someone needs to have some balls to take care.
- 处理这种烂摊子　-喂喂喂
- Of this damn problem! - Hey hey hey!
我们不杀活人
We don't kill the living.
一个拿枪顶着我脑袋的人这么说可真讽刺
That's funny coming from a man who just put a gun to my head.
我跟他很多事情上都不一致
We may disagree on some things,
但这事不会　你把家伙放下
Not on this. You put it down.
快点
Go on.
- 跟我来　-要带我上哪
- Come with me. - Where are you taking me?
安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
我来表示慰问
I came to pay my respects.
我有没有跟你提过
Did I ever mention.
我老婆是怎么没的
How I lost my wife?
- 癌症不是么　-是
- Cancer, wasn't it? - Yeah.
我拉着她看遍了医生
I dragged her to every doctor,
做遍了检查
Every test.
终于在无数手术和化疗之后
And after all the surgeries and the chemos,
她心里准备好了
She was ready.
她接受了事实　知道么
She accepted it, you know?
可我不能
But I never could.
之后那几年我一直过得
And I spent the last few years.
很是恼火
So angry.
我觉得完全被人给耍了
I felt so cheated.
自她去世之后
Since she passed,
你们两个姑娘
You girls were the first people…
是我唯一在乎的人
that I cared anything for.
今天是她生日吗
This is her birthday?
她的生日总是像
Her birthday was always like…
像个七天的盛会
Like a week long affair.
可惜我却总是这样那样地错过
But I somehow always missed it.
我要么在大学里回不去
I was away at college.
或是太忙没时间跟小孩子胡闹
Or too busy for kid's parties.
她总是会很兴奋地打电话给我
She'd call all excited.
而我总是说我肯定到家
I always said that I'd make it home.
说那话的时候我是真心的
And I really always meant to,
可我没有一次兑现了诺言
But I never made it past that phone call.
我明白现实已经足够残酷
I know things are hard enough for you.
就不要再责怪自己了好么
Without adding guilt into the mix, huh?
我来好了　毕竟是我丈夫
I'll do it. He's my husband.
艾米
Amy.
艾米　对不起
Amy, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我总是没能在你身边
For not ever being there.
我总觉得我们会有足够的时间
I always thought there'd be more time.
我现在在了　艾米
I'm here now, amy.
我陪你
I'm here.
我爱你
I love you.
有话就说
Say it.
行
Okay.
我在想如果你当时留下了
I'm thinking if you'd of stayed here,
选择了自己家人
If you'd have looked after your own…
而不是走出去　还带走了一半人手
instead you went off. You took half our manpower with you.
那我们的损失就不会这么惨重了
I'm thinking maybe our losses wouldn't have been so bad.
要不是我们出去把那袋枪捡了回来
If we hadn't gone off and brought those guns back.
我觉得我们的损失可能会更惨
when we did, I think our losses would have been a lot worse.
没准会是一个不留
Maybe the entire camp.
我还是觉得不烧了这些尸体是个错误
I still think it's a mistake not burning these bodies.
我们不是说好了要这么来的么
It's what we said we'd do, right?
烧个干净　一了百了不是
Burn 'em all, wasn't that the idea?
最初是这样
At first.
这位中国仔感情用事了
The chinaman gets all emotional,
说事不能那么来　我们就这么被牵着走了
Says it's not the thing to do, we just follow him along?
人们该知道这他娘的是谁管事
These people need to know who the hell's in charge here,
- 规矩是什么样　-这没有规矩
- What the rules are. - There are no rules.
那就是个问题
Well, that's a problem.
我们都没有哪怕一分钟时间
We haven't had one minute.
来给之前的自己告别
to hold onto anything of our old selves.
我们要时间来哀悼死者　我们要埋葬他们
We need time to mourn and we need to bury our dead.
是人就得这么做
It's what people do.
哦不
Oh no.
不　不　不　不
No no no no.
不要这样　拜托
No, not this, please.
不　不　不
No no no.
不　不　不　不
Oh, no no no.
不　不
No no.
我能行　我能行
I can do it. I can do it.
I can do it! I can do it.
亲手埋葬别人已经够糟了
Burying other people is bad enough,
- 但是一想到我们当中　-嘘
- But the thought of one of us… - Shh.
爸爸　我们现在安全了吗
Are we safe now, dad?
我们现在都在一起了吗
Now that we're together?
我不会再走开了
I won't leave again.
我保证　无论发生什么都不走
I promise you that. Not for anything.
现在你让我和妈妈
Now give me a chance.
单独谈谈话好么
To discuss some things with your mom, okay?
- 好　-乖
- Yeah. - All right.
乖
All right.
肖恩怪我当时没留下
Shane blames me for not being here.
你呢
Do you?
我们现在有枪了　我们强力了
We got guns now. We're stronger.
人数也更少了
And we have fewer people.
我们也更弱了
That makes us weaker.
你想要我说你做对了
You want me to say I think you were right?
我理解
I understand that.
但我只能说你们都各有道理
All I can say is that neither one of you is entirely wrong.
我只能这么说了
It's the best I can do right now.
那疾控中心呢
What about the C.D.C.?
- 瑞克　-我们现在进退两难了
- Rick…　- We're at the ragged edge here.
我们需要救援　还有伤员需要帮助
We need relief and we got a sick man who needs help.
我不知道为什么大家都视而不见
I don't know why people can't see that.
看看大家的神情
Well, look at their faces.
再看看我　大家都吓坏了
Look at mine. We're all terrified.
如果有人根据直觉做个决定
If one of us suggested, based on a hunch,
让我们到城市里去
that we head toward that city,
你就找不到我们了
you'd have no part of it.
告诉我些千真万确的话
Tell me something with certainty.
我爱你
I love you.
这是我唯一确定的东西
That's all I got.
我也爱你
I love you too.
他烧得更厉害了
His fever is worse.
需要什么吗
You need anything?
水　我要喝水
Water. Could use more water.
- 我去拿些来　-好
- I'll get some.　- Okay.
卡萝尔　过来帮忙
Carol, you help me?
你给我留了条命吗
You save a grave for me?
谁都不想弄成那样
Nobody wants that.
你想不想这无所谓
It's not about what you want.
就好比你想自作主张时
That, uh… that sound you hear,
上帝就会嘲笑你一样
that's god laughing while you make plans.
我的想法是　吉姆
What I want, Jim, if…
要是上天允许
If god allows,
你得寻求一些帮助
is to get you some help.
小心红树林
Watch the mangroves.
红树林的根会让船搁浅
Their roots will gouge the whole boat.
你也知道吧
You know that, right?
艾米就在那里游泳
Amy is there swimming.
你会照看好这艘船的吧
You'll watch the boat, right?
你说过的
You said you would.
我会照看好这艘船
I'll watch the boat.
放心吧
Don't worry.
好吧
Okay.
你得去和瑞克谈谈
I need you to help talk some sense into Rick.
听着　洛莉　去疾控中心是个错误
Look, this C.D.C. Thing, Lori, it's a mistake.
这么说你支持他咯
So you're backing him?
我还能怎样　他是我丈夫
What else would I do? He's my husband.
听着　也许你是该做个尽职的妻子
Look, it may be time for you to play the dutiful wife,
但你要弥补自己的婚姻是你的事
but you can't tell me that fixing your marriage.
别把大伙的安全拿去冒险
is worth putting people's lives at risk.
这和我的婚姻无关
I think folks around here can make up.
大伙能自己做出决定
their minds without bringing my marriage into it.
你得改了这个习惯
It's a habit you need to break.
我已经在努力了
I guess I'll just add it to the list of habits that I'm breaking.
这也由不得我
whether I like it or not.
什么习惯
What habits?
我只是说要有个计划　伙计
Just talking about my need for a plan, man.
有结果了吗　我们走还是不走
So what is it? Are we leaving or not?
或许大伙儿只是想留下来
Maybe y'all just want to stay here.
我们还有些罐头食物
We could hang some more tin cans.
我们不能留下　这谁都知道
We can't stay here. We both know that.
我刚也是这意思　我们该相信你的直觉
I was just telling Shane I think we should trust your gut.
我们去巡逻一下
Let's go do our sweep.
跟你说吧　哥们
Tell you what, man,
这些人他们心里没底
These people, man, they're not convinced.
你去疾控中心的主意
You head to the C.D.C.,
可能没人支持
You might be on your own.
你真想让洛莉和卡尔
You gotta really consider whether you want to.
落到这种危险境地吗
put Lori and Carl in that kind of spot.
我得为我的家庭着想
I got to do what's best for my family.
为家人着想　这算哪门子着想
Best for your family? What's that?
- 让他们身处各种险境吗　-什么险境
- Exposing them to all kinds of risks?　- As opposed to what?
又不是跨越100英里的敌占区
Crossing 100 miles of hostile territory?
如果我们命悬一线
If we're looking for a lifeline,
得就近求援
I say swim toward the closest ship,
远水救不了近火
Not further out to sea.
你为什么就不支持我呢
Why can't you back me up?
听着　我也想　只是…
Look, I want to. It's just…
我不懂
I don't see it.
不是你的家人　你当然不明白
If it was your family, you'd feel differently.
你刚说什么
What did you say to me?
是我保护他们的安全　伙计
I kept 'em safe, man.
我视如己出般地保护他们
I looked after them like they were my own.
- 我是这么做的　-我不是那个意思
- That's what I did.　- I didn't mean it that way.
那你什么意思
Well, how'd you mean it?
说啊　你是什么意思
Go on, man. How'd you mean it?
你误解了
you're misinterpreting me.
- 是吗　-我误会了我的意思
- All right.　- You're just hearing it wrong.
- 真的吗　-听着　你也知道
- Yeah?　- Look, you know…
你的恩惠我无以为报　好吗
You know I can never repay that debt, okay?
天啊
Jesus.
我知道
I know.
看来要穿反光背心了　免得误伤自己人
Gonna have to start wearing reflective vests out here.
说真的
Seriously.
来吧　哥们
Come on, man.
走吧　伙计
Come on, man, let's go.
这里啥都没有
Nothing out here.
我想了想瑞克的计划
I've been, uh… I've been thinking about Rick's plan.
听着　这个…
Now look, there are no…
不管怎样都没有任何保证
There are no guarantees either way.
我率先承认这一点
I'll be the first one to admit that.
我和他认识很久了
I've known this man a long time.
我相信他的直觉
I trust his instincts.
我觉得最重要的是　我们得团结在一起
I say the most important thing here is we need to stay together.
如果大家都同意
So those of you that agree,
我们一大早就动身离开
We leave first thing in the morning.
好吗
Okay?
我们要转移了
We're moving out,
离开采石场
Leaving the quarry.
如果你昨天听到我的话　可能已经过来了
If you heard me yesterday, you may be coming here.
这样的话　你到时我们已经走了
If you are, we'll be gone by the time you arrive.
我会给你留下字条和地图
I'm leaving a note and map behind for you.
贴在一辆红车上
taped to a red car.
这样你就能跟上我们了
So you can follow our trail.
我们要去疾控中心
We're heading to the C.D.C.
那里是我们最后的希望
If there's anything left, it's got to be there,
你不觉得吗
don't you think?
摩根
Morgan…
我希望你对那的看法是对的
I hope you were right about that place.
拜托千万别出错
I need you to be.
大家听好了
Everybody listen up.
手上有电台接收器的　我们在40频道
Those of you with C.B.s, we're gonna be on channel 40.
不要弄出很大声响　好吗
Let's keep the chatter down, okay?
如果没有接收器　一旦出了问题
Now you got a problem, don't have a C.B.,
收不到信号　失去联系的话
can't get a signal or anything at all,
要立刻吹号
you're gonna hit your horn one time.
队伍就会停下来
That'll stop the caravan.
- 有问题吗　-我们…
- Any questions? - We're, uh…
我们不去了
We're… we're not going.
我们在伯明翰还有亲戚
We have family in Birmingham.
我们想去投奔他们
We want to be with our people.
你们单独行动的话　就没人能照应你们了
You go on your own, you won't have anyone to watch your back.
我们想赌一把
We'll take the chance.
我得为我的家人着想
I got to do what's best for my family.
- 确定吗　-我们讨论过了
- You sure? - We talked about it.
我们决定了
We're sure.
好吧
All right.
- 肖恩　-好吧
- Shane. - Yeah, all right.
- 点357那把吗　-对
- Dot 357? - Yeah.
里面还有一半子弹
The box is half full.
谢谢你们　一切的一切
Thank you all… for everything.
来
Come here.
祝你好运　伙计
Good luck, man.
感激不尽
Appreciate it.
再见了
Bye.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Bye.
如果改变主意　我们在40频道
Channel 40 if you change your minds.
- 好吗　-好
- All right? - Yeah.
我知道
I know.
你怎么知道我们会更走运
What makes you think our odds are any better?
来吧　动身吧
Come on. Let's go.
出发
Let's move out.
（摩根　去疾控中心　这里不安全　瑞克）
我早说过　这软管撑不了多远
I told you we'd never get far on that hose.
得用那辆小货车上的才行
I said I needed the one from the cube van.
能想办法凑合一下吗
Can you jury-rig it?
我一直在凑合了
That's all it's been so far.
这是管道胶带　不是软管
It's more duct tape than hose.
现在连胶带都没有了
And I'm out of duct tape.
前面好像有东西
I see something up ahead.
走运的话　会是个加油站
A gas station if we're lucky.
各位　吉姆他
Y'all, Jim…
情况不妙　我觉得他快不行了
It's bad. I don't think he can take anymore.
瑞克　你照看一下这边吧
Hey, Rick, you want to hold down the fort?
我开到前面去　看能带回点什么来
I'll drive ahead, see what I can bring back.
我也一起去　照应你一下
Yeah, I'll come along too and I'll back you up.
你们都警惕一点
Y'all keep your eyes open now.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
我们很开就能继续前进
We'll be back on the road soon.
不要　上帝啊
Oh no. Christ.
我的骨头
My bones…
我的骨头好像一触即碎
my bones are like glass.
一点颠簸都…
Every little bump…
上帝　这一路快把我折磨死了
God, this ride is killing me.
把我留在这吧
Leave me here.
我完了
I'm done.
别管我了
Just leave me.
我想跟我的家人团聚
I want to be with my family.
他们都去世了
They're all dead.
我看你都不知道自己在说什么
I don't think you know what you're asking.
是发烧的缘故　你一直都神志不清
The fever… you've been delirious more often than not.
我知道　你以为我不知道吗
I know. Don't you think I know?
我现在清醒得很
I'm clear now.
五分钟后可能就清醒不了了
In five minutes I may not be.
瑞克　我清楚自己在说什么
Rick, I know what I'm asking.
我希望如此
I want this.
别管我了
Leave me here.
责任我来承担
Now that's on me.
好吗
Okay?
是我的决定
My decision.
不是你的失策
Not your failure.
他说他想这样
It's what he says he wants.
他神志清楚吗
And he's lucid?
看来是的
He seems to be.
我会答应的
I would say yes.
在营地时　我说达里尔可能是对的
Back in the camp when I said Daryl might be right.
你让我闭嘴
and you shut me down,
是你误会我了
you misunderstood.
我绝对不会赞同
I would never go along.
无情地结束一个人的生命
with callously killing a man.
我只是想提议
I was just gonna suggest.
问问吉姆的想法
that we ask Jim what he wants.
现在我们知道了
And I think we have an answer.
就把他丢在这里
We just leave him here?
自己走掉吗
We take off?
那我想我不会原谅自己
Man, I'm not sure I could live with that.
这不是你们的事
It's not your call,
你们两个说了都不算
either one of you.
好　就这样
Yeah. That's it.
又是一棵烂树
Hey, another damn tree.
吉姆
Hey, Jim…
你也知道　不一定非得这样
I mean, you know it doesn't need to be this.
不
No.
这样挺好的
It's good.
微风拂面
The breeze feels nice.
好
Okay.
好吧
All right.
闭上眼睛　亲爱的
Just close your eyes, sweetie.
不要硬撑了
Don't fight.
吉姆　你要这个吗
Jim, do you want this?
不了
No.
你自己会用得着
You'll need it.
我没事的
I'm okay.
我没事
谢谢你
Thanks for, uh,
为我们而战
for fighting for us.
好的
Okay.
（野火计划　最高位3417　已启动 开始传输信息）
我是詹纳
Jenner here.
今天是野火计划启动后的第194天
It's day 194 since Wildfire was declared.
也是疾病突然全球爆发后的第63天
and 63 days since the disease abruptly went global.
目前没有临床研究进展需要上报
There's no clinical progress to report.
记录1　我终于把东区的辐射防护器
Item… I finally got the scrubbers.
给关掉了以便节省电力
in the east sector shut down to save power.
真希望一个月前我就能关掉
Wish I could have done it a month ago,
但我花了好久才搞清楚那些机器
but it took me that long to figure it out.
可惜我从没有学过工程
Too bad I never studied engineering.
不然可以省很多电力
Could have saved a lot of amps.
记录2　我还是睡不好觉
Item… I'm still not sleeping well.
作息根本无法规律
Can't seem to keep regular hours.
生活在地下的坏处
Living underground doesn't help,
无法分辨白天黑夜
not knowing if it's day or night.
这些日子我的状态很不好
I'm just feeling very off-kilter these days.
（野火计划　最高位3417　已启动 信息已终止传输）
警备状态
Alert status.
空气探测器警告出现腐蚀性烟雾
Air qualifiers indicate corrosive fumes.
所有人员请立即离开
All personnel must clear the room.
吸入该腐蚀性气体　可致命
Corrosive element is deemed poisonous if inhaled.
所有人员已离开
All personnel clear.
全面消毒已启动
Full decontamination in effect.
不
No!
全面消毒已完成
Full decontamination complete.
第19号试验样本被毁了
The TS19 samples are gone.
这无疑是一大惨痛损失
The tragedy of their loss cannot be overstated.
它们可是迄今为止最新鲜的样本
They were our freshest samples by far.
我们采集的其它样本根本无法与之相比
None of the other samples we gathered even came close.
那些样本都已坏死脱落
Those are necrotic,
都是些无用的坏死组织
useless dead flesh.
我都不知道我干嘛跟你说话
I don't even know why I'm talking to you.
我敢说外面连一个
I bet there isn't a single son of a bitch.
狗杂种的影子都没　对不对
out there still listening, is there?
对不对
Is there?
算了
Fine.
省得我跟你瞎瞪眼
Saves me the embarrassment.
我看明天我还是一枪毙了自己好了
I think tomorrow I'm gonna blow my brains out.
我还没决定好
I haven't decided.
但是今晚
But tonight,
我要不醉不休
I'm getting drunk.
说起这个
Speaking of which,
你觉得我能抛多远呢
how far do you think I can chuck this, huh?
我看铁定很远
Pretty far I bet.
都抛出场外了
It is out of the stadium!
好了　大伙　继续前进　继续走
All right, everybody. Keep moving. Go on.
保持安静　继续走
Stay quiet. Let's go.
好了　继续前进　都跟紧
Okay, keep moving. Stay together.
- 继续前进　快点　-别吵
- Keep moving. Come on. - Shh.
- 卡萝尔　-别吵
- Carol. - Shh.
天呐
Oh, god.
不是吧
No.
大伙跟紧对方　快点
Keep it together. Come on.
我们快到了　宝贝
We're almost there, baby.
快到了
Almost there.
啥都没有吗
Nothing?
里面没人
There's nobody here.
那为啥这些卷帘门都落下了
Then why are these shutters down?
- 有行尸　-宝贝　快点
- Walkers! - Baby, come on.
你把我们送上了死路
You led us into a graveyard!
- 他做的决定　-这决定他妈的错了
- He made a call. - It was the wrong damn call!
闭嘴　你给我闭嘴　给我安静点
Just shut up. You hear shut up. Shut up!
瑞克　这是个死胡同
Rick, this is a dead end.
我们该去哪里
Where are we gonna go?
你听到了吗　别指责了
Do you hear me? No blame.
她说得对　我们不能待在这里
She's right. We can't be here,
天就要黑了　这里离城区太近了
this close to the city after dark.
瑞克　我们可以选择前往本宁堡
Fort Benning, Rick… still an option.
怎么去　没有食物　没有燃料
On what? No food, no fuel.
而且还100英里远
That's 100 miles.
是125英里　我查过地图
125. I checked the map.
去他妈本宁堡　我们今晚该怎么办
Forget Fort Benning. We need answers tonight, now.
- 让我想想办法　-快点　我们走
- Well, think of something. - Come on, let's go.
- 快点离开这　-我们走　快
- Let's get out of here. - Let's go. Please.
好了　大伙都上车
All right, everybody back to the cars.
- 我们走　快点　-摄像头动了
- Let's go. Move. - The camera… it moved.
- 别做梦了　-真的动了
- You imagined it. - It moved.
- 它真的动了　-瑞克　这已经报废了
- It moved. - Rick, it is dead, man.
这是个自动装置　是装置而已　好吗
It's an automated device. It's gears, okay?
不过是机器转了回去　快点走吧
They're just winding down. Now come on.
- 不　走开　-哥们　听我一句
- No, just go away. - Man, just listen to me.
看看四周　这里全报废了　明白吗
Look around this place. It's dead, okay?
别再揪着这里不放了　瑞克
It's dead. You need to let it go, Rick.
瑞克　这里面没人
Rick, there's nobody here!
我知道你在里面　我知道你能听到我说话
I know you're in there. I know you can hear me.
大伙马上都给我回车上去
Everybody get back to the cars now!
求求你　我们已经走投无路了
Please, we're desperate.
请帮帮我们　我们这里有妇女跟孩子
Please help us. We have women, children,
- 没有食物　汽油也快没了　-瑞克
- No food, hardly any gas left. - Rick.
- 里面没有人　-我们无处可去了
- There's nobody here. - We have nowhere else to go.
警惕四周
Keep your eyes open.
你不让我们进去就等于在害死我们
If you don't let us in, you're killing us!
- 求求你了　-快点　哥们　咱们走
- Please! - Come on, buddy, let's go.
- 我们走　-请帮帮我们
- Let's go. - Please help us.
你这是要害死我们　你不能见死不救
You're killing us! You're killing us!
你是要害死我们
You're killing us!